jewelrymakingjournal.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy | Jewelry Making Journal

Privacy policy of https://jewelrymakingjournal.com, effective as of May 23, 2018.

JewelryMakingJournal.com (sometimes “Jewelry Making Journal” or “https://jewelrymakingjournal.com” or “we” or “us”) are committed to protecting your privacy.

“You” refers to the user visiting the https://jewelrymakingjournal.com website.

We value and protect your privacy as much as we value and protect our own.

We will never sell your personal data.

This privacy policy explains how JewelryMakingJournal.com collects, uses, and shares data when you use this website.

### Third-Party Products and Services We Use for Jewelry Making Journal:

  * **Google Analytics**  
Google privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy  
Used by Jewelry Making Journal for website analytics  
Data collected: Cookies, usage data
  * **Teachable.com**  
Teachable.com Privacy Policy: https://teachable.com/privacy-policy/  
Used by Jewelry Making Journal for providing educational products  
Data collected: name, email address, IP address.
  * **Aweber.com**  
Aweber Privacy Policy: http://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm  
Used by Jewelry Making Journal for newsletter subscriber list management, mailout service, and autoresponder content delivery.  
Data collected: your email address, IP address.
  * **Gravity Forms by Rocketgenius**  
Gravity Forms privacy policy: https://www.gravityforms.com/terms-and-conditions/  
Used by Jewelry Making Journal for creating custom forms. 
    * Used for Jewelry Making Journal Contact form:  
Data collected: your email address, IP address, your optional message.
    * Used for Jewelry Making Journal product support help messages:  
Data collected: Name, email address, phone number.
    * Used for Jewelry Making Journal guest content submissions:  
Data collected: Name, email address, IP address;  
Optional data collected for guest posts: city/state/country, website/facebook page URL, the images and text you submit.
  * **Thrive Themes**  
Thrive Themes privacy policy: https://thrivethemes.com/privacy-policy/  
Used by Jewelry Making Journal for website theme.  
Data collected by theme:  
As with most websites, the JewelryMakingJournal.com hosting collects and uses the data contained in log files. The information in the log files includes your IP address (internet protocol), your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit this site, the time you visited this site and which pages you visited throughout this site. 

Data collected from the comments on JewelryMakingJournal.com posts:  
Your name, email address, and your optional website URL as typed in by you; and your IP address; your Gravatar from gravatar.com (if you have one).

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

We do not knowingly collect data from anyone under age 13 years, in compliance with COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). Although JewelryMakingJournal.com is “G-Rated” or “family friendly” content, our content is not directed to individuals who are age 13 or younger.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

JewelryMakingJournal.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed, and will provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy so you understand the data we collect and how we use it.

### Agreeing to These Terms

If you do not agree to JewelryMakingJournal.com’s Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

Thank you.

### Contact / Request Your Data

To request a copy of your data that we’ve stored about your usage of this website, use the contact information below. We will send you a copy of these data within 30 days.

To request that we delete your data, use the contact information below. We will delete the data within 72 hours.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us:

**By Email Contact Form:**  

**By Postal Mail:**  
Rena Klingenberg  
Jewelry Making Journal  
P.O. Box 21242  
Albuquerque, NM 87154
